http://www.ilcusa.org/privacy-policy

Internet Learning Center Respects Your Privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Internet Learning Center.
Credit Card Details
Internet Learning Center will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Internet Learning Center.
External Sites
Internet Learning Center is not responsible for the content of external internet sites.
You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Internet Learning Center to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc).
Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Internet Learning Center does not use cookies to collect personal information.
Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember the Risks Whenever You Use the Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Internet Learning Center and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.
In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Internet Learning Center have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
For any further information please email webmaster.
